♪ Here we are going far ♪
♪ to save all that we love ♪
♪ If we give all we’ve got ♪
♪ we will make it through ♪
♪ Here we are like a star ♪
♪ shining bright
on your world today ♪
♪ Make evil go away ♪
♪ Code Lyoko we’ll
withstand it all ♪
♪ Code Lyoko be there
when you call ♪
♪ Code Lyoko we
will stand real tall ♪
♪ Code Lyoko
stronger after all ♪
Aelita, do you read me?
Yes, Jeremie. Hi!
All alone?
Where are the others?
They’re out playing soccer.
But I was feeling tired.
Tired? That’s interesting.
Jeremie, how do humans
know when they feel tired?
Well, you feel like
you don’t have any energy.
Like having weak batteries,
and so we rest a while.
And is resting
something you like doing?
I used to find it really boring,
but ever since I met you, Aelita,
it’s such a pleasure
hanging out together.
It is for me, too, Jeremie.
Hey, Ulrich, pass it over here!
You won’t get by me!
Oh!
I don’t believe it, oh!
Oh, no!
Another g-o-o-a-l!
Seven to one!
This is turning into a rout!
Huh, it sure is!
Okay, guys. It’s getting late.
I’ve got to head for home.
Okay. So long, Yumi.
See you tomorrow!
You guys are so bad!
What a couple of losers!
Do you guys need a little help?
Who are you, huh?
Theo. I’m new around here.
I just moved into town.
Wow, and I like this school already!
Hi, my name is Sissi.
Mhmm…
And these two friends of mine
are Herb and Nicholas,
the worst soccer
players you ever saw!
Nice to meet you.
Uh…
Odd’s the name.
And he’s Ulrich.
Hi, Theo. Welcome.
Do you play?
Sure do! Let’s go!
Which team should I play with?
We don’t need you, okay?
I thought you were down seven to one.
What do you think, Sissi?
Why not? Yeah, okay!
It sure can’t get any worse!
Alright, Jeremie. I’m here.
Okay, we’re looking for the tower
where part of the
scanner programs are stored.
It’s at 30 degrees north, Aelita.
I’m on my way.
As soon as you’re connected,
I’ll download the data that you find.
It’ll help me understand
materialization better.
Okay, guys.
We’ve gotta stop, it’s time for dinner.
Nine-seven! We beat ’em!
What do you think, princess?
Theo saved you guys
from humiliation!
Who cares about soccer?
It’s a dumb game!
If you ask me,
Herb’s got it in for Theo.
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
Great, peas and carrots
for the umpteenth time.
Sissi…
Ha-ha-hah! Hey!
Hey! Why don’t you
eat with us, champ?
Thanks a lot,
but I can’t abandon my team!
You mind?
Hey, stop trying
to worm your way in!
You’re not in our group,
so go take a hike!
Well, yeah. I know, Herb,
but I’d love to join your group,
or should I say Sissi’s group?
Is that it?
Uh, what do I have to do?
Well, you’ve gotta pass our Initiation tests
and they’re really dangerous and hard!
Much too hard for you!
Initiation tests?
Tell me a little about them!
Test number one! Uh, you have to…
clean all the toilets with a toothbrush!
That sounds like a pretty dumb test.
That’s like the kind they give to
10-year-olds at summer camp,
so I’ll pass on that one.
Okay! Since you refused
to pass our test, ciao!
Hey!
Since when do you
decide on the tests?
I’ll tell you what you have to do.
You’re gonna mummify the skeleton
we use in the science room.
Okay, now that sounds cool!
(CHUCKLES)
Jeremie, did you manage
to gather all the data?
I did, but it won’t do any good.
Not unless I can pirate the access
codes for the scanner programs.
But that’s almost impossible!
No, Aelita, I think It can be done.
Okay, they’ve left their rooms!
We’ll tell you all about
operation Theo later!
Here I go!
Still a long way to go…
(LAUGHS)
What are you gonna do, Herb?
I’m gonna warn our old friend, Jim!
They’ll kick Theo out of school,
and we’ll be home free!
(HOWLING)
Huh?
What was that weird sound?
(HOWLING)
Aaaaaaaaaaaah!
(LAUGHING)
Nice work, little ghost!
What are you two guys doing here?
It’s okay. We were gonna tell you.
Hey, things look serious
between Sissi and Theo.
Yeah, they sure do.
You finished lunch already?
No, but I wanna see Aelita
for a while before class.
I wouldn’t mind either.
We’ll go together, okay?
Leave your trays!
It’s a shame to let
good desserts go to waste.
Odd, don’t you ever stop eating, huh?
Mmm!
Odd, you’re gonna explode
if you keep this up.
Nah.
Aah!
Hey!
Which region are you in now?
I was just in the forest,
and I thought I sensed
some pulsations, but I’m not sure.
XANA?
I’ll call Jeremie.
(RINGS)
Jeremie, weird things are
happening in the lunchroom.
Could be XANA’s doing.
Why?
What’s the problem?
There are short circuits everywhere.
Aelita, could you
check things out on Lyoko?
I will.
I’ll launch a scan to see
if XANA has activated a tower.
Let’s get out of here.
Aaaaah!
Hey, Odd!
Odd!
Oh, no.
I wasn’t mistaken.
Tower localized.
Jeremie, there are very strong
pulsations in the forest.
Yeah, the scan confirms it.
And Odd and Ulrich
are trapped in the cafeteria.
Yumi, I’ll head for the factory.
Warn the principal,
and then meet me over there.
(KNOCKING)
Come in.
Uh, can I see you for a minute, sir?
Please, it’s important.
Did you see that?
Jim! Are you okay?
Oh, Jim, say something!
Are you alright?
We’ve got to cut the current now!
Hello, is that you, dad?
We don’t know what happened!
Move!
There’s electricity everywhere.
We’re trying to
break a window to get out.
I’ve got to get out!
Ulrich, what’s going on?
We’re prisoners here
n the cafeteria, Jeremie.
I’ll send Yumi to Lyoko.
We’ll do our best over here.
Yumi, hurry up.
We don’t have a lot of time.
I told the principal.
I’m at the passage in the park now.
What is this?
I just cut all the power!
With no effect at all!
The firemen are on the way.
I have no idea what XANA
wants to do this time.
What about in town?
Have any of the
other buildings been hit?
No, that’s why I’m worried.
We’ll get out of this.
Don’t worry, Herb.
Lemme go, will ya?
Everything will be okay.
Help is on the way.
There, you see?
We could try the roof.
It’s probably the same.
It’s worth trying.
Outta the way!
It’s like a prison.
But how come XANA’s
set his sights on the cafeteria?
It makes no sense at all.
He can’t gain access to the city
through the school.
He probably has other ideas.
Wait, I think I understand!
It’s the four of us he’s after!
Us? You sure?
Yumi and I left lunch before dessert.
If not, we’d have all been there.
He wanted to catch us all together!
XANA hasn’t missed a trick this time.
We’re never gonna get out of here.
You’ve got to play for time.
Yumi’s alone, she’s gonna need every
second she can to protect Aelita.
We’ll do the best we can.
Jeremie, the pulsations
are really intense here.
The tower can’t be too far.
Stay where you are.
I programmed the position.
Yumi’s on her way.
Transfer Yumi.
Scanner Yumi.
Virtualization.
The pulsations radiate
in two directions.
Jeremie, any news?
Give me a little time
to analyze the terrain.
I’m getting contradictory signals.
Impossible to tell
which path is the right one!
Well, we have no choice.
Each of us will explore one path.
We’ll stay in contact via Jeremie.
Let’s go!
You see?
This way, even if the
walls cave in, we’ll be safe.
The roof won’t fall on top of us.
Watch out!
Sissi! What’s going on?
Answer me, child! Sissi!
Jeremie, how are
things going with Aelita?
Nothing to report for now,
and no monster in sight.
That’s really strange, it’s too easy!
Should I go on?
I’ll call you back in 30 seconds.
A quick analysis of the surroundings…
I gotta get out!
Wait! No, don’t, Herb!
The electricity! It’s live!
Leave me alone!
Take it easy, Herb. Calm down!
You’ve got to.
You understand, hm?
I’m stuck.
This tunnel has got to lead somewhere.
It’s got to lead to the path
that Aelita took.
Here I go.
Jeremie…
Hold on, Aelita.
Aelita!
Two monsters are on the way!
You’re surrounded by two Krabs!
Run!
It’s impossible, Jeremie!
I cut off all the wires, chief!
I doubt that. Nothing’s changed.
Have the firemen really
tried everything, Daddy?
They’re going to keep trying, dear.
We’ll be okay, you’ll see.
Jeremie, have you got anything new?
I’m trying, Ulrich.
Aelita, can you hear me?
Oh, no!
Stay out of sight, Aelita!
Yumi’s almost there!
(CELESTIAL HUMMING)
Yumi will get here in time.
I know she will.
I have faith in you, Jeremie.
Oh, no!
I have faith in you.
That’s what I call
getting carried away.
(CHUCKLES)
Sissi, darling,
you mustn't give up hope.
The firemen are going to
make an opening in the roof.
There’s gotta be a passage
leading to the path that goes to the towers!
There.
It’s all over now!
Thanks for what you did before.
I was pretty awful to you.
Jeremie, this is urgent! Come on!
They’re almost there!
Watch it, a third Krab is on the way!
There it is!
No, leave him!
Go on, now! Hurry!
Don’t worry about me.
Hiyah!
Good shot, Yumi,
but he’s only damaged.
But you took 20 life points from him.
One more shot, and he’ll be done for!
Aelita’s entering the tower.
Phew.
Return to the past now!
Hey Ulrich, pass it over here!
You won’t get by me!
Oh!
I don’t believe it! Oh!
Oh, no!
G-o-o-o-a-l! Ha-ha-ha!
Unbelieveable!
You losers!
Okay, guys.
I’ve got to head for home.
If you want,
I’ll walk you back home--
No, I’ll go!
So long, Odd, and thanks!
So, uh, which way do we go, huh?
What’s wrong?
It’s a lot better than having to
get up tonight to scare Herb, right?
Don’t you think?
What’s wrong! Come on, Ulrich!
You’re toast, dude.
You’re never satisfied.
You got a better idea?
No? Well, me neither!
CLOSED CAPTIONING PROVIDED BY
REDDIT.COM/R/CODELYOKO